### **Bibek Dulal**

Campsie, NSW 2194 M: 0434539613

E: bbekdulal07@gmail.com

L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bibek-dulal/

P: https://bibekdulal.com/

## **Professional Profile**

A passionate graduate equipped with a diverse and promising skill set with a background in Information Technology from Federation University Australia. Skilled and experienced in various programming language and tools such as JavaScript, ReactJS, jQuery, Python, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tail CSS, and SQL. Willing to embrace additional training and development.

#### **Technical Skills**

**Programming Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python

Framework ReactJS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tail CSS, SCSS, LESS

Computer Systems: Windows, Mac OS, Linux, Android

Web Servers: Apache Web Server

**Databases:** MySQL, Firebase, Microsoft Access

Computer Software: Microsoft Suite (Office, Excel, PowerPoint, Visio, Project), SharePoint,

WordPress, Photoshop

**Version Control System:** Git

API Rest API

# Soft skills

- Problem solving and critical thinking.
- Strong Communication and Interpersonal Skills.
- Proactive, initiative and work well in team.
- Attention to detail.

### **Personal Projects**

## **Netflix Clone Website**

**Objective:** To replicate Netflix homepage design.

**Tools:** ReactJS, Axios, HTML & CSS

**Outcome:** Successfully created Netflix clone using data sourced from The Movie Database API.

**Link:** https://github.com/bibs07/netflix-clone-reactjs

## **TikTok Clone Website**

**Objective:** To replicate TikTok design and functionality using the data stored in Firebase database.

**Tools:** ReactJS, Firebase, HTML & CSS

**Outcome:** Successfully created TikTok clone using data sourced from Firebase database.

Link: <a href="https://github.com/bibs07/tiktok-clone-reactJS">https://github.com/bibs07/tiktok-clone-reactJS</a>

Bibek Dulal 1

**Calculator** 

**Objective:** To create a programme able to handle basic calculation.

**Tools:** jQuery, Bootstrap & HTML

**Outcome:** Successfully created calculator which can take use input and print the result.

Link: <a href="https://github.com/bibs07/calculator-jQuery">https://github.com/bibs07/calculator-jQuery</a>

### **Personal Portfolio Website**

**Objective:** To create a protfolio website to display brief summary about myself.

Tools: ReactJS, Tail CSS, HTML & CSS

Outcome: Successfully created portfolio website.

**Link:** https://github.com/bibs07/personal-portfolio-react

# **Employment History**

## **Barbeques Galore Australia**

Sales Assistant Apr 2018 – Mar 2021

# Assistant Store Manager Mar 2021 - Current

# **Duties and Responsibilities**

• Quickly determined customer's needs, and developed a solution to fit the scope of issue

- Supervised and trained teams of part-time and full-time employees in sales, merchandising, and inventory control
- Educated and trained customers to troubleshoot products when applicable to prevent unnecessary return visits.
- Aimed to develop a keen awareness of customer wants and desires.

## **Education**

# **Bachelor of Information Technology (Programming Major)**

Mar 2018 - Dec 2020

Federation University Australia

Achievements: High Distinction and Distinction average in almost all software related subjects

### References

References will be provided on request.

Bibek Dulal 2